Meddlesome.
A man.
You two
are quite skilled.
What brings you
to Er City?
None of your business.
In Er City,
every brick, tile, person, and object
is related to my master.
Since you're here.
Then don't be in a rush to leave.
Either stay as guests of Ercheng
and serve my master,
or in another way,
stay here forever.
So many monsters.
So according to you,
Ercheng doesn't belong to the government,
but to your master?
The government? Hahaha.
Those two old dogs in the government,
if it weren't for our master's generosity,
we would have eaten them long ago.
Say no more, everyone.
What will you do?
Make your choice.
This Taoist priest's idea...
Naturally, I wouldn't dare to make wild guesses.
But I'd like to propose another option.
Why not have your master give this outer city to me?
Serve me well,
and I will surely lead you
to a brighter future.
How about it?
Have mercy, Daoist Master!
Save me!
No matter.
You can handle it.
Divine Taiji.
Qiankun Alignment.
Nanming Lihuo.
Boundless Blazing Flames.
Li Position,
activate!
Thank you so much for just now.
It was nothing.
Don't mention it.
Sister Gesang,
you hurt your hand.
It's just a scratch.
It's bleeding a lot. Let me bandage it for you.
Don't touch my blood.
Thanks. I'll handle it myself.
Put your clothes on.
How do I wear this?
Never mind.
First thing tomorrow morning,
go buy yourself a new outfit.
Okay.
And you.
Didn't I tell you
not to follow me anymore?
Master Daoist, it's not appropriate to say that now.
If I weren't here,
you would have been fighting five against one.
They are not the mortals from the wilderness inn.
Sister,
you're wrong about that.
Even if the Master fought five against one,
he wouldn't lose.
He can turn into an immortal. A great immortal!
Master,
you heard it just now.
The demons in Ercheng are more than just these.
I am Gesang.
Seeing that you are quite interested in this,
why don't we team up?
We can investigate it together.
I am used to acting alone.
No need to trouble yourself.
We have things to do at the government office tomorrow morning.
Farewell.
Master! Master!
Where are you going?
Back to my room.
We are still staying here?
Or else,
you can find another place.
No, no.
I am safer following you.
Master,
teach me that move you just did.
Shut up.
I still underestimated you.
Wake up.
Master.
Wake up, Master.
Master, this...
Go away.
You didn't sleep all night.
How could I dare to sleep?
What if more monsters come?
I've already set up a barrier around us.
Monsters won't get in so easily.
You should have told me earlier.
Master, it's already dawn.
Let's hurry to the yamen.
I've never seen you this active before.
Once we hand over the goods,
we can get out of this dump.
Not 'we'.
After the goods are handed over,
you go your way,
and I go mine.
From then on, your business has nothing to do with me.
Morning.
Have some breakfast.
Ercheng is so weird.
It's so lively at night,
but there isn't even a single breakfast stall in the morning.
I brought this myself. Try some.
Try it.
You are so sweet.
Eat more.
Since ancient times, official lands have been protected by gods.
Now the immortal magic here is very weak.
The magical objects are broken,
and their power is gone.
It seems
what the cat demon said last night was true.
Kid.
Report to the officials!
What's the matter?
Hey, I, I, I...
What are you doing?
Report to the officials!
Report to the authorities.
Muqiang Haihui.
Pingjie Qianghai.